

Rodrigo

Developer



14 July 1983



Londrina - PR, Brazil



+55 43 999-108-629



http://goo.gl/F2v0o5



rodfersou@gmail.com

# About me -

I am passionate about the art of creating computer programs.

As you can see by looking at my experience, I worry much more about building a solid foundation of knowledge than on taking the banner of a particular language. I consider myself able to accept the challenge of working in any environment, language, database or platform.

# Design Patterns Javascript Python CSharp Delphi Java

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

SOL

## interests

Good challenges, which demand concentration and focus on quality deliveries.

## education

2011-2012 Web Development Specialization course.

Use of offline web pages in the inventory of assets process.

2008-2009 Software Engineering and Database Specialization course.

Generating code from a class diagram to an object-relational mapper.

2002-2006 Computer Engineering Graduation.

Adaptive assistant to access classroom tools.

2000-2001 Data Processing Technical course.

Development of a library management system.

### experience

2015-Atual	Team leader Simples Consultoria Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)
2014-2015	Software architect Anicet Corporação Analysis and development of big data systems and generation of marketing information for e-commerce. (Python / MongoDB)
2012-2014	Developer AVADORA digital Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)
2013-2014	Systems Analyst AGILI Softwares para Área Pública Analysis and development of systems and web portals. (CSharp / Oracle)
2011-2012	Senior Systems Analyst MÓDULOS RECAP SOFTWARE LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for tire retreaders. (Delphi / Firebird)
2011-2011	ABAP Developer PADO SA INDUST. COMERCIAL E IMPORTADORA Customization of SAP ERP screens and reports. (ABAP)
2009-2011	Systems Analyst Maxwell Bohr Instrumentação Eletrônica Development of applications for automation devices. (Python / C / C ++)
2009-2009	Systems Analyst ADVISE DO BRASIL Development and maintenance of application for automated processing of electronic texts. (Delphi / SQL Server)
2008-2009	Systems Analyst  Development and maintenance of GPRS and Satellite messaging server.  (CSharp / SQL Server)
2006-2008	Developer Amcor Flexibles Brasil LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for flexibles industry. (Progress 4GL)
2003-2006	Senior Systems Analyst Jabur Informática Development and maintenance of ERP for vehicle dealers. (Progress 4GL)

## languages

English	Understand Well, Speak Well, Read Well, Write Well.
Spanish	Understand Well, Speak Reasonably, Read Reasonably, Write Little.
Japanese	Understand Reasonably, Speak Little, Read Little, Write Little,